<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloudback</title>
    <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/categories/cloudback/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cloudback</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.cloudback.it/categories/cloudback/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is a bare git repository and how Cloudback uses it?</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/git-bare-repo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/git-bare-repo/</guid>
      <description>A Git bare repository represents a specialized form of a Git repository, distinct in structure and function from a conventional Git repository. Platforms like GitHub utilize bare repositories on their servers. Essentially, when a user initiates a clone command from GitHub, they are interacting with a bare repository stored on GitHub&amp;rsquo;s server. This type of repository is optimized for server-side storage and facilitates efficient and secure management and distribution of code, without the direct editing capabilities found in standard repositories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 crucial features of Backup Software that will benefit your Business</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/5-crucial-features-of-backup-software-that-will-benefit-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/5-crucial-features-of-backup-software-that-will-benefit-your-business/</guid>
      <description>Your business can be susceptible to losing data. Worse, it can sometimes catch you off guard, causing delays and disruptions in your operations. Prevent that from happening by investing in the enterprise backup software for your business.
According to a report by Varonis, companies have over 1,000 sensitive files and 100,000 folders accessible and open to their employees. Businesses are vulnerable from data corruption, deletion, leaks, and breaches—whether intentional or accidental.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudback introduces new marketplace plans</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/paid-plans-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/paid-plans-announcement/</guid>
      <description>Today we reached 100+ installations and completed GitHub Marketplace financial onboarding. Now Cloudback meets all the requirements for GitHub Marketplace, including listing, billing, brand, and user experience requirements. It means that we completed the public beta stage, and now Cloudback is in production with no limits.
We are glad to announce, that our new marketplace plans are available in the GitHub Marketplace!
 Our Free Plan remains active for all existing accounts but is discontinued and is no longer available for new users.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
