<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Cloudback</title>
    <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Cloudback</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://docs.cloudback.it/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automated Backups</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/automated-daily-backups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/automated-daily-backups/</guid>
      <description>Automated Daily Backups This is why we created Cloudback - to continuously backup a repository and its metadata on a daily basis. By default, Cloudback captures a backup daily at a defined hour according to a defined time zone and puts a resulting archive into defined storage. You can also create a custom schedule to run your backups on non-daily basis.
Schedule You can configure the exact hour you want to capture a backup every day, or define your own schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon S3 Bucket via Access Key</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/amazon-s3-bucket-access-key/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/amazon-s3-bucket-access-key/</guid>
      <description>Backup GitHub repository using Amazon S3 Bucket Access Key About Amazon S3 Bucket Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) is an object storage service that offers industry-leading scalability, data availability, security, and performance. This means customers of all sizes and industries can use it to store and protect any amount of data for a range of use cases, such as data lakes, websites, mobile applications, backup and restore, archive, enterprise applications, IoT devices, and big data analytics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon S3 Bucket via Access Point</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/amazon-s3-bucket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/amazon-s3-bucket/</guid>
      <description>Backup GitHub repository using Amazon S3 Bucket About Amazon S3 Bucket Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) is an object storage service that offers industry-leading scalability, data availability, security, and performance. This means customers of all sizes and industries can use it to store and protect any amount of data for a range of use cases, such as data lakes, websites, mobile applications, backup and restore, archive, enterprise applications, IoT devices, and big data analytics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a new Microsoft Azure Blob Container</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/microsoft-azure-blob-container/create-microsoft-azure-blob-container/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/microsoft-azure-blob-container/create-microsoft-azure-blob-container/</guid>
      <description>Backup GitHub repository using Azure: How to create a new Microsoft Azure Blob Container When creating GitHub repository backup using Cloudback you can set up your own Azure Storage where the backups will be saved. This article describes how to create a new Azure Blob Container for GitHub repository backups.
About Microsoft Azure Blob Containers Azure Blob storage is Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s object storage solution for the cloud that is optimized for storing massive amounts of unstructured data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Various Backup Storages</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/various-backup-storages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/various-backup-storages/</guid>
      <description>Various Backup Storages Cloudback allows you to store a backup archive in your own storage, leaving no copies to us. That is. Cloudback backs up a repository into an archive, sends the archive to your storage, and wipes the archive from Cloudback&amp;rsquo;s disk leaving no chance to recover any data from the Cloudback servers.
Also, we offer our in-build storage named just Cloudback.
Register your storage In order to tell Cloudback to store backups into your own storage, please use the + New storage button in the settings of the repository card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Cloudback</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/what-is-cloudback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/what-is-cloudback/</guid>
      <description>What is Cloudback Cloudback is the cloud backup service for GitHub repositories.
The main feature is the support of various backup storages. When user storage is configured we do not store backup archives inside Cloudback infrastructure at all. All archives are put into your storage. In case you don&amp;rsquo;t have your own storage there is still an option to use our internal storage called Cloudback.
It uses the official GitHub REST API to access repository metadata for backups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon S3 Glacier</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/amazon-s3-glacier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/amazon-s3-glacier/</guid>
      <description>Backup GitHub repository using Amazon S3 Glacier About Amazon S3 Glacier Amazon S3 Glacier and S3 Glacier Deep Archive are secure, durable, and extremely low-cost Amazon S3 cloud storage classes for data archiving and long-term backup. They are designed to deliver 99.999999999% durability, and provide comprehensive security and compliance capabilities that can help meet even the most stringent regulatory requirements.
 Set up Amazon S3 Glacier as a custom storage  In the Cloudback Dashboard open the repository settings by clicking on the settings icon:    Click on the + New storage button:     Type a storage name</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a new shared access signature (SAS)</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/microsoft-azure-blob-container/create-shared-access-signature/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/microsoft-azure-blob-container/create-shared-access-signature/</guid>
      <description>Backup GitHub repository using Azure: How to create a new shared access signature When creating GitHub repository backup using Cloudback you can set up your own Azure Storage where the backups will be saved. If you want to use Azure Storage for backups created by Cloudback you need to provide Cloudback access to your storage, which should be done by creating a new Shared Access Signature (SAS) inside your Azure Container.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metadata Backups</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/metadata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/metadata/</guid>
      <description>Metadata Backups Cloudback archives not only the whole git repository but GitHub-specific metadata as well. The list of metadata we are able to backup is not complete and is limited by the GitHub API.
Important things to know:
 We don&amp;rsquo;t backup your GitHub Account We don&amp;rsquo;t backup your GitHub Organization The resulting backup should never be considered as a complete all-embracing one  What is included in a backup? Here is the list of repository&amp;rsquo;s data in a backup archive:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud Storage Bucket</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/google-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/google-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Backup GitHub repository using Google Cloud Storage Bucket About Google Cloud Storage Bucket Cloud Storage allows world-wide storage and retrieval of any amount of data at any time. You can use Cloud Storage for a range of scenarios including serving website content, storing data for archival and disaster recovery, or distributing large data objects to users via direct download.
 Set up Google Cloud Storage Bucket  In the Cloudback Dashboard open the repository settings by clicking on the settings icon:    Click on the + New storage button:     Type a storage name</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft OneDrive</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/onedrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/onedrive/</guid>
      <description>Backup GitHub repository using Microsoft OneDrive About Microsoft OneDrive OneDrive is the cloud storage service that Microsoft offers to store all your files securely in one place, which you can then access from virtually anywhere.
 Set up Microsoft OneDrive Personal:App&amp;rsquo;s Folder  In the Cloudback Dashboard open the repository settings by clicking on the settings icon:    Click on the + New storage button:    Type a storage name:     Select Microsoft OneDrive Personal:App&#39;s Folder</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One-Click Manual Backups</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/manual-backups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/manual-backups/</guid>
      <description>One-Click Manual Backups Cloudback allows you to trigger a backup process on demand by clicking a single button. There are several use-cases when manual backups are useful:
 You want to download your up-to-date data, no need to wait for an automatic trigger You want to test your own storage that you configured recently You want to secure your data at a specific point in time  Trigger a backup Once your repository is scheduled, just click a button and trigger a backup, that&amp;rsquo;s all:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alibaba Cloud Object Storage Service</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/alibaba-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/alibaba-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Backup GitHub repository using Alibaba Cloud Object Storage Service About Alibaba Cloud Object Storage Service Alibaba Cloud Object Storage Service (OSS) is an encrypted, secure, cost-effective, and easy-to-use object storage service that enables you to store, back up, and archive large amounts of data in the cloud, with a guaranteed durability of 99.9999999999%(12 9’s). RESTful APIs allow storage and access to OSS anywhere on the Internet. You can elastically scale the capacity and processing capability and choose from a variety of storage types to optimize the storage cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download Backups</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/download-backups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/download-backups/</guid>
      <description>Download Backups You can download an archive of any backup of your repositories. There is the Download this backup button in the repository card:
Download dialog Once you click the Download this backup button the dialog will be shown. The dialog reminds you that the archive&amp;rsquo;s password will be sent to your email right after the download process is initiated.
Archive&amp;rsquo;s password email You will receive an email with the password each time you download a password-protected archive of a repository backup:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started This is a short instruction describing how to start creating backups for your GitHub repositories.
Installation Follow these simple steps below to start using Cloudback.
Step 1: Set up a new plan from the GitHub Marketplace  Open Cloudback&amp;rsquo;s page on the GitHub Marketplace by clicking on the following link Click on the Set up a plan button.   In the Pricing and Setup section select the account for which the Cloudback application will be installed and then click on the Install it for free button   Review your order to make sure you&amp;rsquo;ve selected the correct plan and account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restore to GitHub</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/restore-to-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/restore-to-github/</guid>
      <description>Restore to GitHub Cloudback allows you to restore any backup to a new GitHub repository. This is a manual process, accessible from the repository card in the Cloudback Dashboard.
Prerequisites The restore process requires read and write access to your GitHub data, but the Cloudback app has read-only access, following the principle of least privilege. We have released an additional application Cloudback Restore with read and write access to your data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email Notifications</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/email-notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/email-notifications/</guid>
      <description>Email Notifications If something goes wrong and a backup process fails, we will send you an email notification. We send a daily notification at 22:00 UTC with all failed automatic backups in the last 24 hours.
Once a backup has failed, our support team will also be notified. If the problem is not related to storage, the team will start investigating as soon as possible and notify you of the results via email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instant Notifications</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/instant-notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/instant-notifications/</guid>
      <description>Instant Notifications Cloudback supports real-time notifications via messenger services:
Instant Notifications about successful and failed backups can be configured per account in the &amp;lsquo;Notification Settings&amp;rsquo; dialog of the main menu of Cloudback Dashboard. All notifications are Webhook based. Webhooks are user-defined HTTP URL callbacks. They are usually triggered to facilitate integration of different applications, in our particular case it is Cloudback and a Messenger. Within a Messenger, you can create an Incoming Webhook for a text channel and get a URL for created Webhook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Organizations</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/github-organizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/github-organizations/</guid>
      <description>GitHub Organizations Cloudback supports shared team accounts called GitHub Organization. You can purchase a paid plan in GitHub Marketplace for your organization&amp;rsquo;s account and repositories will appear in Cloudback Dashboard. This way several team members may configure and control backups for your organizations using a single shared dashboard.
Please note that only organization members with the role Owner will be able to access the organization&amp;rsquo;s repositories in Cloudback.
Learn more   GitHub: About organizations  GitHub: Permission levels for an organization  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invoiced Customers</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/invoiced-customers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/invoiced-customers/</guid>
      <description>Invoiced Customers If you have a GitHub Enterprise account and you pay GitHub by invoice - you will not able to purchase Cloudback&amp;rsquo;s paid plans using the GitHub Marketplace. If you try to purchase a paid plan on GitHub Marketplace you will get an error message Unfortunately, invoiced customers cannot purchase paid plans on the GitHub Marketplace.
The good news is that there is a workaround and Cloudback supports direct payments using bank transfers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wasabi</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/wasabi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/custom-storages/wasabi/</guid>
      <description>Backup GitHub repository using Wasabi About Wasabi  Wasabi is a public cloud object storage service that is 1/5th the price of Amazon S3 and faster than the competition with no fees for egress or API requests. Wasabi provides 11 x 9s of data durability, high system availability, and support for immutable storage buckets. Wasabi is fully compatible with the Amazon S3 API with support for hundreds of S3-compatible storage applications and has been certified for compliance with enterprise security and privacy standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bulk Operations</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/bulk-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/bulk-operations/</guid>
      <description>Bulk Operations If you have a large number of repositories it is not comfortable to manage their settings using Cloudback Dashboard with the card-based user interface. Cloudback offers the Bulk Operations dialog instead. The dialog allows you to apply settings to many repositories with a single click.
Repository name pattern Repository name pattern accepts wildcard characters and a comma character to join multiple queries:
Wildcard characters:
* - zero or more characters ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incident Response Plan</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/security/incident-response-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/security/incident-response-plan/</guid>
      <description>Incident Response Plan Introduction The purpose of the document is to establish the goals and the vision for the incident management process in the MYRTLE GROUP S.A. (“we” or “Cloudback”). This document discusses the steps taken during an incident response plan.
Incident Response Process  The person who discovers the incident should contact Cloudback by one of the following ways:   Send an email to the support@cloudback.it Raise a request in the Cloudback issue tracker Use any contacts from Contact Us web page   If the person discovering the incident is a member of the Cloudback team, they will proceed to step four (4).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup Status Badge</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/status-badges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/status-badges/</guid>
      <description>Backup Status Badge The badge represents the status of the latest backup created by Cloudback. The badge can be embedded into any web page. Here is the badge:
 
You can find a sample usage in the Cloudback&amp;rsquo;s Documentation repository home page: https://github.com/cloudback/docs#readme</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Password-Protected Archives</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/archive/</guid>
      <description>Password-Protected Archives The archive represents ZIP File Version 5.2 with AES-256 encryption. Be aware that AES encryption is not widely supported by ZIP tools and archivers. For instance, Microsoft Windows Compressed Folders does not support AES encryption and isn&amp;rsquo;t able to open any AES-encrypted ZIP archive. Please consider using third-party software. We recommend you 7-Zip which is cross-platform and is free for commercial use (there are limitations, please refer to 7-Zip License for details).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Deduplication</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/deduplication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/deduplication/</guid>
      <description>Data Deduplication With data deduplication, you can save a significant amount of cloud storage space and reduce operational costs. Cloudback offers a simple but efficient technique of data deduplication.
How deduplication works Our backup archives are deterministic. If nothing has changed in a GitHub repository, we create the same archive before encrypting it. Once the archive is encrypted, the AES encryption makes it non-deterministic.
Cloudback compares the checksum of a new deterministic backup with a previous deterministic backup before encrypting it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Card View</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/card-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/card-view/</guid>
      <description>Card View It is a default view for Cloudback Dashboard, extremely simple and user friendly. Suitable for small number of repositories and basic scenarios.
Card Controls The schema below depicts all buttons on the card
Front side of the card Here you can find the next functionality:
 The status of the repository The list of latest backups Trigger backup manually Restore arbitrary backup Download an archive of arbitrary backup  Back side of the card Here you can find the next functionality:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Table View</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/table-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/table-view/</guid>
      <description>Table View Advanced screen for managing a large number of repositories.
Table Controls The schema below depicts all buttons on the table
Main Grid Here you can find the next functionality:
 The list of repositories and their statuses Sorting and filtering Checkboxes for triggering multiple backups at once  Repository Settings Here you can find the next functionality:
 Toggle scheduled/not scheduled  don&amp;rsquo;t forget to press Save button   Set up schedule/retention/storage for the repository  Backups and Restores Here you can find the next functionality:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Schedules</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/custom-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/custom-schedule/</guid>
      <description>Custom Schedules Cloudback provides build-in schedules for daily backups out of the box. If you want to backup on a weekly or monthly basis, you can create your own schedule using the Schedule Manager from the Main Menu. Once you create your own schedule, it becomes available in the Schedule dropdown box of repository settings.
Example: Every Monday Morning Schedule Let&amp;rsquo;s create Every Monday Morning schedule for weekly backups step-by-step:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disaster Recovery Plan Policy</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/security/disaster-recovery-plan-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/security/disaster-recovery-plan-policy/</guid>
      <description>Disaster Recovery Plan Policy Overview The purpose of the policy is to establish the goals and the vision for the disaster recovery process in the MYRTLE GROUP S.A. (&amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Cloudback&amp;rdquo;). It is important to understand that having a contingency plan in the event of a disaster gives Cloudback a competitive advantage. This policy requires management to financially support and diligently attend to disaster contingency planning efforts. Disasters are not limited to adverse weather conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Breach Response Policy</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/security/data-breach-response-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/security/data-breach-response-policy/</guid>
      <description>Data Breach Response Policy Purpose The purpose of the policy is to establish the goals and the vision for the breach response process in the MYRTLE GROUP S.A. (&amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Cloudback&amp;rdquo;). This policy will clearly define to whom it applies and under what circumstances, and it will include the definition of a breach, staff roles and responsibilities, standards and metrics (e.g., to enable prioritization of the incidents), as well as reporting, remediation, and feedback mechanisms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability Management Workflow</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/security/vulnerability-management-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/security/vulnerability-management-workflow/</guid>
      <description>Vulnerability Management Workflow Introduction The purpose of the document is to describe the established vulnerability management workflow in the MYRTLE GROUP S.A. (“we” or “Cloudback”).
Overview Vulnerability Management is the recurring process of identifying, classifying, prioritizing, mitigating, and remediating vulnerabilities. This document will focus on infrastructure vulnerabilities and the vulnerability management process. This process is designed to provide informationregarding Cloudback vulnerability workflow, promote healthy patch management among other preventative best-practices, and remediate risk; all with the end goal to better secure our environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We support a new storage now: Wasabi Cloud Storage</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/wasabi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/wasabi/</guid>
      <description>Cloudback provides an easy way to store GitHub repository backups in various storages. And today, we are delighted to announce the support of a new storage - Wasabi Cloud Storage.
Wasabi provides simple, predictable and affordable hot cloud storage for businesses all over the world. It enables organizations to store and instantly access an infinite amount of data at 1/5th the price of the competition with no complex tiers or unpredictable egress fees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New feature: Table View</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/table-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/table-view/</guid>
      <description>The Cloudback team is happy to announce that an alternative view for Cloudback Dashboard is released. It is a Table View. Using table view it is much easier to navigate through a large number of repositories and trigger on-demand backups. We put the Table View Toggle in the header, so it is always easy to switch to the Table View and back to the Card View. It was a feature request of our client and we are glad to deliver it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instant notifications of successful and failed backups</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/instant-notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/instant-notifications/</guid>
      <description>Four months ago, in February 2022, we received a new feature request from our user in our issue tracker. In the request, the user asked us to implement real-time notification support via messengers. As soon as a backup fails or succeeds, he should receive a notification. We found the request extremely useful and prioritized it in the backlog of our project. Despite the delay in delivery, we are happy to say that the work is done and the feature is now available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New feature: You can enable data deduplication to reduce storage costs</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/data-deduplication/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/data-deduplication/</guid>
      <description>The Cloudback team is pleased to announce a new feature: Data deduplication for custom storage. The use case is a daily backup for a GitHub repository that&amp;rsquo;s not changed every day. The feature prevents wasting storage space just because Cloudback saves backup archives with the same content every day, even though nothing has changed in your GitHub repository. In certain scenarios, the feature can drastically reduce storage costs.
 The configuration of all existing custom storages remains unchanged and data deduplication is disabled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive encryption is now optional</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/optional-password-protection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/optional-password-protection/</guid>
      <description>For security reasons, Cloudback uses AES-256 encryption for all backup archives. If you download a specific backup, you can access its content using the password. The password is sent automatically to your GitHub account primary email. However, some people may find this approach a little bit overcomplicated, especially when using custom storage somewhere inside your own secure infrastructure.
We are glad to announce that it is possible to opt-out of password-based encryption now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We added custom email address for notifications</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/notifications-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/notifications-email/</guid>
      <description>Cloudback sends an email notification to the user if the backup fails. By default, we are using the primary email address taken from the GitHub profile.
We received a feature request to support custom emails for notifications. This may be useful when you have a separate email for such kinds of notifications. We decided to provide such functionality for every account where the Cloudback GitHub Application is installed. Now you can set up a new email address for failed backup notifications for each account using the Account Settings dialog:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 crucial features of Backup Software that will benefit your Business</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/5-crucial-features-of-backup-software-that-will-benefit-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/5-crucial-features-of-backup-software-that-will-benefit-your-business/</guid>
      <description>Your business can be susceptible to losing data. Worse, it can sometimes catch you off guard, causing delays and disruptions in your operations. Prevent that from happening by investing in the enterprise backup software for your business.
According to a report by Varonis, companies have over 1,000 sensitive files and 100,000 folders accessible and open to their employees. Businesses are vulnerable from data corruption, deletion, leaks, and breaches—whether intentional or accidental.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We support new storage now: Microsoft OneDrive</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/onedrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/onedrive/</guid>
      <description>Cloudback provides an easy way to store GitHub repository backups in various storages. And today, we are delighted to announce the support of new storage - Microsoft OneDrive.
We received a request to support this storage via email, but to make our work more transparent, we created a related issue in our public issue tracker. The development process from the initial request to a production-ready solution took about a month, including two weeks of waiting for the verification from the Microsoft side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We support new storage now: OpenStack Swift</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/openstack-swift/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/openstack-swift/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, we got a new feature request in our issue tracker. One of Cloudback users asked us to add support for the OpenStack Swift storage provider. We discussed the feature request within the team and started development. We decided to use an S3 API gateway of OpenStack Swift. As a side effect, we introduced an S3 access-key-based provider in addition to OpenStack Swift. Now Cloudback supports any S3 API compatible storage provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudback introduces new marketplace plans</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/paid-plans-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/paid-plans-announcement/</guid>
      <description>Today we reached 100+ installations and completed GitHub Marketplace financial onboarding. Now Cloudback meets all the requirements for GitHub Marketplace, including listing, billing, brand, and user experience requirements. It means that we completed the public beta stage, and now Cloudback is in production with no limits.
We are glad to announce, that our new marketplace plans are available in the GitHub Marketplace!
 Our Free Plan remains active for all existing accounts but is discontinued and is no longer available for new users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First public release of Cloudback</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/first-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/first-release/</guid>
      <description>Our team is proud to announce to you the first public release of Cloudback - GitHub repository backup as a service. The decision to start the Cloudback project has been made a few months ago when we noticed there are no solutions that provide the ability to back up a GitHub repository into private cloud storage. We made this a key feature of our product - the integration with various cloud storage providers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
