<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Cloudback</title>
    <link>https://cloudback.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Cloudback</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cloudback.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon S3 Bucket</title>
      <link>https://cloudback.github.io/custom-storages/amazon-s3-bucket/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudback.github.io/custom-storages/amazon-s3-bucket/</guid>
      <description>Amazon S3 Bucket Page is under development</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a new Microsoft Azure Blob Container</title>
      <link>https://cloudback.github.io/custom-storages/microsoft-azure-blob-container/create-microsoft-azure-blob-container/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudback.github.io/custom-storages/microsoft-azure-blob-container/create-microsoft-azure-blob-container/</guid>
      <description>How to create a new Microsoft Azure Blob Container About Microsoft Azure Blob Containers Azure Blob storage is Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s object storage solution for the cloud that is optimized for storing massive amounts of unstructured data. Unstructured data is data that doesn&amp;rsquo;t adhere to a particular data model or definition, such as text or binary data. Azure Storage is a Microsoft-managed service that provides highly available, secure, durable, and scalable cloud storage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon S3 Glacier</title>
      <link>https://cloudback.github.io/custom-storages/amazon-s3-glacier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudback.github.io/custom-storages/amazon-s3-glacier/</guid>
      <description>Amazon S3 Glacier Page is under development</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a new shared access signature (SAS)</title>
      <link>https://cloudback.github.io/custom-storages/microsoft-azure-blob-container/create-shared-access-signature/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudback.github.io/custom-storages/microsoft-azure-blob-container/create-shared-access-signature/</guid>
      <description>How to create a new shared access signature About shared access signatures A shared access signature (SAS) provides secure delegated access to resources in your storage account. With a SAS, you have granular control over how a client can access your data. For example:
 What resources the client may access What permissions they have to those resources How long the SAS is valid  This page describes how to create a new SAS for your storage container.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud Storage Bucket</title>
      <link>https://cloudback.github.io/custom-storages/google-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudback.github.io/custom-storages/google-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Google Cloud Storage Bucket Page is under development</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alibaba Cloud Object Storage Service</title>
      <link>https://cloudback.github.io/custom-storages/alibaba-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudback.github.io/custom-storages/alibaba-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Alibaba Cloud Object Storage Service Page is under development</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incident Response Plan</title>
      <link>https://cloudback.github.io/security/incident-response-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudback.github.io/security/incident-response-plan/</guid>
      <description>Incident Response Plan Introduction The purpose of the document is to establish the goals and the vision for the incident management process in the MYRTLECONSULTING S.A. (“we” or “Cloudback”). This document discusses the steps taken during an incident response plan.
Incident Response Process  The person who discovers the incident should contact Cloudback by one of the following ways:   Send an email to the support@cloudback.it Raise a request in the Cloudback issue tracker Use any contacts from Contact Us web page   If the person discovering the incident is a member of the Cloudback team, they will proceed to step four (4).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disaster Recovery Plan Policy</title>
      <link>https://cloudback.github.io/security/disaster-recovery-plan-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudback.github.io/security/disaster-recovery-plan-policy/</guid>
      <description>Disaster Recovery Plan Policy Overview The purpose of the policy is to establish the goals and the vision for the disaster recovery process in the MYRTLECONSULTING S.A. (&amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Cloudback&amp;rdquo;). It is important to understand that having a contingency plan in the event of a disaster gives Cloudback a competitive advantage. This policy requires management to financially support and diligently attend to disaster contingency planning efforts. Disasters are not limited to adverse weather conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Breach Response Policy</title>
      <link>https://cloudback.github.io/security/data-breach-response-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudback.github.io/security/data-breach-response-policy/</guid>
      <description>Data Breach Response Policy Purpose The purpose of the policy is to establish the goals and the vision for the breach response process in the MYRTLECONSULTING S.A. (&amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Cloudback&amp;rdquo;). This policy will clearly define to whom it applies and under what circumstances, and it will include the definition of a breach, staff roles and responsibilities, standards and metrics (e.g., to enable prioritization of the incidents), as well as reporting, remediation, and feedback mechanisms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability Management Workflow</title>
      <link>https://cloudback.github.io/security/vulnerability-management-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudback.github.io/security/vulnerability-management-workflow/</guid>
      <description>Vulnerability Management Workflow Introduction The purpose of the document is to describe the established vulnerability management workflow in the MYRTLECONSULTING S.A. (“we” or “Cloudback”).
Overview Vulnerability Management is the recurring process of identifying, classifying, prioritizing, mitigating, and remediating vulnerabilities. This document will focus on infrastructure vulnerabilities and the vulnerability management process. This process is designed to provide informationregarding Cloudback vulnerability workflow, promote healthy patch management among other preventative best-practices, and remediate risk; all with the end goal to better secure our environments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>