<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloudback</title>
    <link>https://cloudback.github.io/how-to/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cloudback</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cloudback.github.io/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a new Microsoft Azure Blob Container</title>
      <link>https://cloudback.github.io/how-to/create-microsoft-azure-blob-container/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudback.github.io/how-to/create-microsoft-azure-blob-container/</guid>
      <description>How to create a new Microsoft Azure Blob Container About Microsoft Azure Blob Containers Azure Blob storage is Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s object storage solution for the cloud that is optimized for storing massive amounts of unstructured data. Unstructured data is data that doesn&amp;rsquo;t adhere to a particular data model or definition, such as text or binary data. Azure Storage is a Microsoft-managed service that provides highly available, secure, durable, and scalable cloud storage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a new shared access signature (SAS)</title>
      <link>https://cloudback.github.io/how-to/create-shared-access-signature/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudback.github.io/how-to/create-shared-access-signature/</guid>
      <description>How to create a new shared access signature About shared access signatures A shared access signature (SAS) provides secure delegated access to resources in your storage account. With a SAS, you have granular control over how a client can access your data. For example:
 What resources the client may access What permissions they have to those resources How long the SAS is valid  This page describes how to create a new SAS for your storage container.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>