<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Cloudback</title>
    <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Cloudback</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cloudback transitions from MYRTLE GROUP S.A. to MYRTLELABS S.A.S. for Enhanced Security</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/myrtlelabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/myrtlelabs/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce the beginning of our transition from MYRTLE GROUP S.A. to a dedicated legal entity, MYRTLELABS S.A.S. as a step towards achieving SOC 2 certification. This transition will further strengthen our security posture and allow us to deliver an even more reliable and secure experience for our customers.
A step towards SOC2 certification This transition is the first step in our journey towards achieving SOC2 certification, a globally recognized independent auditing standard for security, availability, and confidentiality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a bare git repository and how Cloudback uses it?</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/git-bare-repo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/git-bare-repo/</guid>
      <description>A Git bare repository represents a specialized form of a Git repository, distinct in structure and function from a conventional Git repository. Platforms like GitHub utilize bare repositories on their servers. Essentially, when a user initiates a clone command from GitHub, they are interacting with a bare repository stored on GitHub&amp;rsquo;s server. This type of repository is optimized for server-side storage and facilitates efficient and secure management and distribution of code, without the direct editing capabilities found in standard repositories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudback Introduces Amazon S3 Object Lock Support for Enhanced GitHub Repository Backup Security</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/s3-object-lock/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/s3-object-lock/</guid>
      <description>Cloudback announces the latest addition to its robust suite of features: support for Amazon S3 Object Lock. This enhancement will enable developers to further strengthen the security and protection of their GitHub repository backups stored on Amazon S3.
Amazon S3 Object Lock is a feature that provides an additional layer of security by enabling users to enforce retention policies and prevent the accidental or malicious deletion of their critical data. By integrating this functionality, Cloudback users can now benefit from the highest level of data protection available for their repository backups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudback introduces regional storages</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/regions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/regions/</guid>
      <description>The Cloudback Team is excited to announce the addition of regional storage options for our clients. If you&amp;rsquo;re utilizing Cloudback Storage for your repositories, you can now select from a variety of storage regions to best suit your needs. See the list of supported storage locations below:
   Storage name Region     Cloudback US USA East, N. Virginia   Cloudback EU EU Central, Amsterdam   Cloudback UK EU West, London   Cloudback Sidney Asia, Australia, Sidney   Cloudback Singapore Asia, Singapore    By default, all backups are stored in the Cloudback US storage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We support a new storage now: Wasabi Cloud Storage</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/wasabi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/wasabi/</guid>
      <description>Cloudback provides an easy way to store GitHub repository backups in various storages. And today, we are delighted to announce the support of a new storage - Wasabi Cloud Storage.
Wasabi provides simple, predictable and affordable hot cloud storage for businesses all over the world. It enables organizations to store and instantly access an infinite amount of data at 1/5th the price of the competition with no complex tiers or unpredictable egress fees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New feature: Table View</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/table-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/table-view/</guid>
      <description>The Cloudback team is happy to announce that an alternative view for Cloudback Dashboard is released. It is a Table View. Using table view it is much easier to navigate through a large number of repositories and trigger on-demand backups. We put the Table View Toggle in the header, so it is always easy to switch to the Table View and back to the Card View. It was a feature request of our client and we are glad to deliver it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instant notifications of successful and failed backups</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/instant-notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/instant-notifications/</guid>
      <description>Four months ago, in February 2022, we received a new feature request from our user in our issue tracker. In the request, the user asked us to implement real-time notification support via messengers. As soon as a backup fails or succeeds, he should receive a notification. We found the request extremely useful and prioritized it in the backlog of our project. Despite the delay in delivery, we are happy to say that the work is done and the feature is now available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New feature: You can enable data deduplication to reduce storage costs</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/data-deduplication/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/data-deduplication/</guid>
      <description>The Cloudback team is pleased to announce a new feature: Data deduplication for customer managed storage. The use case is a daily backup for a GitHub repository that&amp;rsquo;s not changed every day. The feature prevents wasting storage space just because Cloudback saves backup archives with the same content every day, even though nothing has changed in your GitHub repository. In certain scenarios, the feature can drastically reduce storage costs.
 The configuration of all existing customer managed storages remains unchanged and data deduplication is disabled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive encryption is now optional</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/optional-password-protection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/optional-password-protection/</guid>
      <description>For security reasons, Cloudback uses AES-256 encryption for all backup archives. If you download a specific backup, you can access its content using the password. The password is sent automatically to your GitHub account primary email. However, some people may find this approach a little bit overcomplicated, especially when using customer managed storage somewhere inside your own secure infrastructure.
We are glad to announce that it is possible to opt-out of password-based encryption now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We added custom email address for notifications</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/notifications-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/notifications-email/</guid>
      <description>Cloudback sends an email notification to the user if the backup fails. By default, we are using the primary email address taken from the GitHub profile.
We received a feature request to support custom emails for notifications. This may be useful when you have a separate email for such kinds of notifications. We decided to provide such functionality for every account where the Cloudback GitHub Application is installed. Now you can set up a new email address for failed backup notifications for each account using the Account Settings dialog:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 crucial features of Backup Software that will benefit your Business</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/5-crucial-features-of-backup-software-that-will-benefit-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/5-crucial-features-of-backup-software-that-will-benefit-your-business/</guid>
      <description>Your business can be susceptible to losing data. Worse, it can sometimes catch you off guard, causing delays and disruptions in your operations. Prevent that from happening by investing in the enterprise backup software for your business.
According to a report by Varonis, companies have over 1,000 sensitive files and 100,000 folders accessible and open to their employees. Businesses are vulnerable from data corruption, deletion, leaks, and breaches—whether intentional or accidental.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We support new storage now: Microsoft OneDrive</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/onedrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/onedrive/</guid>
      <description>Cloudback provides an easy way to store GitHub repository backups in various storages. And today, we are delighted to announce the support of new storage - Microsoft OneDrive.
We received a request to support this storage via email, but to make our work more transparent, we created a related issue in our public issue tracker. The development process from the initial request to a production-ready solution took about a month, including two weeks of waiting for the verification from the Microsoft side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We support new storage now: OpenStack Swift</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/openstack-swift/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/openstack-swift/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, we got a new feature request in our issue tracker. One of Cloudback users asked us to add support for the OpenStack Swift storage provider. We discussed the feature request within the team and started development. We decided to use an S3 API gateway of OpenStack Swift. As a side effect, we introduced an S3 access-key-based provider in addition to OpenStack Swift. Now Cloudback supports any S3 API compatible storage provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudback introduces new marketplace plans</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/paid-plans-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/paid-plans-announcement/</guid>
      <description>Today we reached 100+ installations and completed GitHub Marketplace financial onboarding. Now Cloudback meets all the requirements for GitHub Marketplace, including listing, billing, brand, and user experience requirements. It means that we completed the public beta stage, and now Cloudback is in production with no limits.
We are glad to announce, that our new marketplace plans are available in the GitHub Marketplace!
 Our Free Plan remains active for all existing accounts but is discontinued and is no longer available for new users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First public release of Cloudback</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/first-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/posts/first-release/</guid>
      <description>Our team is proud to announce to you the first public release of Cloudback - GitHub repository backup as a service. The decision to start the Cloudback project has been made a few months ago when we noticed there are no solutions that provide the ability to back up a GitHub repository into private cloud storage. We made this a key feature of our product - the integration with various cloud storage providers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
