<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloudback</title>
    <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cloudback</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://docs.cloudback.it/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automated Backups</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/automated-daily-backups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/automated-daily-backups/</guid>
      <description>Automated Daily Backups This is why we created Cloudback - to continuously backup a repository and its metadata on a daily basis. By default, Cloudback captures a backup daily at a defined hour according to a defined time zone and puts a resulting archive into defined storage. You can also create a custom schedule to run your backups on non-daily basis.
Schedule You can configure the exact hour you want to capture a backup every day, or define your own schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudback Managed Storages</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/cloudback-storages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/cloudback-storages/</guid>
      <description>Cloudback Managed Storages Cloudback provides a set of managed storages accessible to all clients. To adhere to data residency regulations, these storage facilities are located in various regions. Clients can freely select the storage option nearest to their location without incurring extra fees. By default all backups are stored in the Cloudback US storage.
The list of cloudback managed storages    Storage name Region     Cloudback US USA East, N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Managed Storages</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/customer-storages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/customer-storages/</guid>
      <description>Customer Managed Storages Cloudback allows you to store a backup archive in your own storage, leaving no copies to us. That is. Cloudback backs up a repository into an archive, sends the archive to your storage, and wipes the archive from Cloudback&amp;rsquo;s disk leaving no chance to recover any data from the Cloudback servers.
Also, we offer our in-build storages named according to the storage location: Cloudback US, Cloudback EU, Cloudback UK, Cloudback Sidney, and Cloudback Singapore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Repository Metadata Backup</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/metadata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/metadata/</guid>
      <description>Metadata Backups Cloudback archives not only the whole git repository but GitHub-specific metadata as well. The list of metadata we are able to backup is not complete and is limited by the GitHub API.
Important things to know:
 We don&amp;rsquo;t backup your GitHub Account We don&amp;rsquo;t backup your GitHub Organization The resulting backup should never be considered as a complete all-embracing one  What is included in a backup? Here is the list of repository&amp;rsquo;s data in a backup archive:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One-Click Manual Backups</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/manual-backups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/manual-backups/</guid>
      <description>One-Click Manual Backups Cloudback allows you to trigger a backup process on demand by clicking a single button. There are several use-cases when manual backups are useful:
 You want to download your up-to-date data, no need to wait for an automatic trigger You want to test your own storage that you configured recently You want to secure your data at a specific point in time  Trigger a backup Once your repository is scheduled, just click a button and trigger a backup, that&amp;rsquo;s all:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download Backups</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/download-backups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/download-backups/</guid>
      <description>Download Backups You can download an archive of any backup of your repositories. There is the Download this backup button in the repository card:
Download dialog Once you click the Download this backup button the dialog will be shown. The dialog reminds you that the archive&amp;rsquo;s password will be sent to your email right after the download process is initiated.
Archive&amp;rsquo;s password email You will receive an email with the password each time you download a password-protected archive of a repository backup:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restore to GitHub</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/restore-to-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/restore-to-github/</guid>
      <description>Restore to GitHub Cloudback allows you to restore any backup to a new GitHub repository. This is a manual process, accessible from the repository card in the Cloudback Dashboard.
Prerequisites The restore process requires read and write access to your GitHub data, but the Cloudback app has read-only access, following the principle of least privilege. We have released an additional application Cloudback Restore with read and write access to your data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email Notifications</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/email-notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/email-notifications/</guid>
      <description>Email Notifications If something goes wrong and a backup process fails, we will send you an email notification. We send a daily notification at 22:00 UTC with all failed automatic backups in the last 24 hours.
Once a backup has failed, our support team will also be notified. If the problem is not related to storage, the team will start investigating as soon as possible and notify you of the results via email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instant Notifications</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/instant-notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/instant-notifications/</guid>
      <description>Instant Notifications Cloudback supports real-time notifications via messenger services:
Instant Notifications about successful and failed backups can be configured per account in the &amp;lsquo;Notification Settings&amp;rsquo; dialog of the main menu of Cloudback Dashboard. All notifications are Webhook based. Webhooks are user-defined HTTP URL callbacks. They are usually triggered to facilitate integration of different applications, in our particular case it is Cloudback and a Messenger. Within a Messenger, you can create an Incoming Webhook for a text channel and get a URL for created Webhook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Organizations</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/github-organizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/github-organizations/</guid>
      <description>GitHub Organizations Cloudback supports shared team accounts called GitHub Organization. You can purchase a paid plan in GitHub Marketplace for your organization&amp;rsquo;s account and repositories will appear in Cloudback Dashboard. This way several team members may configure and control backups for your organizations using a single shared dashboard.
Please note that only organization members with the role Owner will be able to access the organization&amp;rsquo;s repositories in Cloudback.
Learn more   GitHub: About organizations  GitHub: Permission levels for an organization  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invoiced Customers</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/invoiced-customers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/invoiced-customers/</guid>
      <description>Invoiced Customers For those who hold GitHub Enterprise accounts and/or settle their GitHub payments through invoices, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that you will not be able to acquire paid plans from Cloudback via the GitHub Marketplace. Any attempts to do so will result in an error message Unfortunately, invoiced customers cannot purchase paid plans on the GitHub Marketplace.
However, there is a positive twist to this situation. Cloudback provides an alternative option in the form of direct bank transfers for payment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bulk Operations</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/bulk-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/bulk-operations/</guid>
      <description>Bulk Operations If you have a large number of repositories it is not comfortable to manage their settings using Cloudback Dashboard with the card-based user interface. Cloudback offers the Bulk Operations dialog instead. The dialog allows you to apply settings to many repositories with a single click.
Repository name pattern Repository name pattern accepts wildcard characters and a comma character to join multiple queries:
Wildcard characters:
* - zero or more characters ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup Status Badge</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/status-badges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/status-badges/</guid>
      <description>Backup Status Badge The badge represents the status of the latest backup created by Cloudback. The badge can be embedded into any web page. Here is the badge:
 
You can find a sample usage in the Cloudback&amp;rsquo;s Documentation repository home page: https://github.com/cloudback/docs#readme</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Password-Protected Archives</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/archive/</guid>
      <description>Password-Protected Archives The archive represents ZIP File Version 5.2 with AES-256 encryption. Be aware that AES encryption is not widely supported by ZIP tools and archivers. For instance, Microsoft Windows Compressed Folders does not support AES encryption and isn&amp;rsquo;t able to open any AES-encrypted ZIP archive. Please consider using third-party software. We recommend you 7-Zip which is cross-platform and is free for commercial use (there are limitations, please refer to 7-Zip License for details).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Deduplication</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/deduplication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/deduplication/</guid>
      <description>Data Deduplication With data deduplication, you can save a significant amount of cloud storage space and reduce operational costs. Cloudback offers a simple but efficient technique of data deduplication.
How deduplication works Our backup archives are deterministic. If nothing has changed in a GitHub repository, we create the same archive before encrypting it. Once the archive is encrypted, the AES encryption makes it non-deterministic.
Cloudback compares the checksum of a new deterministic backup with a previous deterministic backup before encrypting it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Card View</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/card-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/card-view/</guid>
      <description>Card View It is a default view for Cloudback Dashboard, extremely simple and user friendly. Suitable for small number of repositories and basic scenarios.
Card Controls The schema below depicts all buttons on the card
Front side of the card Here you can find the next functionality:
 The status of the repository The list of latest backups Trigger backup manually Restore arbitrary backup Download an archive of arbitrary backup  Back side of the card Here you can find the next functionality:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Table View</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/table-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/table-view/</guid>
      <description>Table View Advanced screen for managing a large number of repositories.
Table Controls The schema below depicts all buttons on the table
Main Grid Here you can find the next functionality:
 The list of repositories and their statuses Sorting and filtering Checkboxes for triggering multiple backups at once  Repository Settings Here you can find the next functionality:
 Toggle scheduled/not scheduled  don&amp;rsquo;t forget to press Save button   Set up schedule/retention/storage for the repository  Backups and Restores Here you can find the next functionality:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Schedules for Automatic GitHub Backups</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/custom-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/custom-schedule/</guid>
      <description>Custom Schedules Cloudback provides build-in schedules for daily backups out of the box. If you want to backup on a weekly or monthly basis, you can create your own schedule using the Schedule Manager from the Main Menu. Once you create your own schedule, it becomes available in the Schedule dropdown box of repository settings.
Example: Every Monday Morning Schedule Let&amp;rsquo;s create Every Monday Morning schedule for weekly backups step-by-step:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon S3 Object Lock</title>
      <link>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/s3-object-lock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.cloudback.it/features/s3-object-lock/</guid>
      <description>Amazon S3 Object Lock  Amazon S3 Object Lock is a feature provided by Amazon Web Services in their Simple Storage Service. It&amp;rsquo;s designed to help you protect your data from being accidentally or intentionally deleted or overwritten. Cloudback supports S3 Object Lock feature for customer-managed storages and allows you to enable it for your backups.
Key Benefits of Amazon S3 Object Lock Support   Enhanced Data Protection: With Amazon S3 Object Lock, you can implement retention policies to ensure your GitHub repository backups remain untouched during a specified period.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
